

Ezequiel Olivera

BARBACK/BARTENDER

ABOUT ME

I'm a 21 year old Hotel Management student on a journey of learning and growth. Alongside my studies, I've spent 8 months immersing myself in the world of hospitality as a barback and bartender. I am in search of a position that can enhance my expertise as a bartender, barback, or waiter.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Birth date

16/08/2002

Nationality

Argentinian/Chilean

Location

Mendoza, Argentina

CONTACT

- ezequieloliverabartender@gmail.com
- +5492615029394
- ezequielolivera.vercel.app
- ezequiel-olivera

WORK EXPERIENCE

Barback/Bartender (Practices)

BUFFALO

- April 2023 April 2023
- Assisted bartenders with food, drinks, and other supplies
- Maintained a clean and organized bar area - Ensured all glasses and mugs were clean and ready for service
- Assisted with the setup and breakdown of the bar area
- Demonstrated a professional, courteous, and friendly attitude
- Make some drinks
- Prepared garnishes

Barback/Bartender

GUILLERMO CARAM PRODUCCIONES.

January 2023 - Present

- Prepares and maintains the bar area, including restocking and tidying.
- Ensures bar is adequately stocked and equipped.
- Assists bartenders in mixing drinks and preparing garnishes.
- Cleans glasses, utensils, and bar equipment.
- Keeps the bar stocked with ice, glasses, and other supplies.
- Make some drinks
- Follows all company policies and procedures.

EDUCATION

Bartender Course (without certificate)

PRIVATE LESSONS (FROM A BARTENDER)

April 2023 - June 2023

Professional Bartender Diploma

August - 2023 EDUTIN ACADEMY

Studying Superior Technique

TECLAB SUPERIOR INSTITUTE (ONLINE AND ASYNCHRONOUS)

June 2023 - Present

HARD SKILLS

Maintain Cleanliness of Bar		Replenish Bar Supplies	Prepare Cocktails	
Prepare Bar Station	Prepare Cocktail Ingredients		Maintain Bar Area	

SOFT SKILLS

Professionalism	Responsibility	Positive Attitude	Customer Service	Cooperation
Conflict Resolution Attention to Detail		Detail		

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH B2 (EF SET) SPANISH NATIVE PORTUGUESE A1-A2